How we doing?
>> How you guys doing? How you guys doing?
>> Doing freaking awesome.
>> Yes, sir. Yes, sir. Man, thank you, man.
Thank you.
>> Spencer and you guys
either one of you guys, just how excited
are you to be here at Cleveland? I know
yesterday.
>> Yeah, you know, I mean, like just, you
know, um a blessing honestly. Um, it
it's just, you know, a dream come true,
honestly. Uh, and when, you know,
when I heard my name call, you know, uh,
it was just, you know, um, excitement.
>> Yeah, I'm I'm so excited. I mean, I feel
like, you know, just got to be honest,
one of my first thoughts was I don't get
to I don't have to play Miles Garrett on
Sundays. So, that's uh something to be
excited about in itself. But I mean,
just to be here, um to be here, be with
these teammates, to be able to um play
for these fans, it's it's an honor.
>> To follow up on that, I mean, left
tackle come through here before and talk
about going up against Miles and that
challenge that it is. How much are you
looking forward to getting that
opportunity in training camp practices
even?
>> I am so excited. I mean, I feel like
there's no way there's no better way for
me to get better than going against
someone like that. I mean, just maybe
the best player in the world. So, um, to
go against him every day is going to be
a blessing.
>> Both of you guys, you you've talked
about versatility, you know, positional
versatility. How much more important is
that becoming in football that, you
know, you're not just a left tackle or a
right tackle or an outside receiver? How
much more important do you feel like
it's it's becoming in the game?
>> Yeah, you know, um you know, uh it's
much more important now. Um you know, um
the more things you can do, um the
better your value is. Um the faster you
learn um the more plays you get. Um you
know uh just you know just you know
being able just you know being just you
know being able to play just being able
to play you know all across the field
you know um it's just going to you know
open up you know uh
many more opportunities. Yeah, man. It's
And you never know what's going to
happen on the football field. Like
someone could go down. Um I think it's
it's a good thing to be able to fill in
wherever I need to. Um yeah, it's it's a
big thing. And then not only that, is
that knowing how to play uh multiple
different positions just broadens or
I don't know, it broadens your knowledge
on the game itself um on how every play
works. So I feel like there's nothing
but positives that come with knowing
multiple positions.
>> You were probably uh playing when games
and Chador Sanders was playing
>> but have you had a chance to to watch
him play and what will it be like to
catch?
>> Yes sir. So um I actually got you know
um kind of like story. Um, so whenever I
had entered the transfer portal, um, my,
uh, after my sophomore season, um, I had
actually went down to Colorado and, you
know, um, you know, uh, and met Shadur,
um, you know, um, he's, you know, um, a
great guy, a great leader. Um, just, you
know, I just I just I just cannot wait
to, you know, build that, you know,
relationship, build that, you know, and
and build that, you know, um,
connection with them.
>> What was it like for you to hear Andrew
Barry say to you on the phone yesterday
during your draft call, uh, that they
expect you to be their left tackle,
their franchise left of the future? I
mean, sure, I'm ready or I feel like
it's it was such it's such a cool thing
to be believed in, and I'm not one that
likes to let people down. So,
>> Spencer, Andrew told us not to be fooled
by your personality, right? I think you
said, "Don't be fooled by your
kindness." Is there a switch that just
flips with you when you step on the
field?
>> Um,
I I guess you could say that. I guess
you could say that. I don't know.
There's just something about I don't
know. There's something about just
ah I don't know that's a little corny.
So let me think of something else.
All right. But it's like the same thing
saying there's no greater joy of moving
a man from point A to point B against
his will. There's really nothing like
it. You know when you're just pushing a
guy back he's like swinging at your
arms. Like there's no feeling like that.
And then to be able to put someone in
the dirt that's it's awesome.
>> Talked about Joe Thomas a little bit
yesterday. Um, first of all, his he
reached out to you yet since you've been
drafted?
>> Uh, no. No. But
>> what drew you to him when you're growing
up watching left tackles and what stood
out about his game where you just called
him the best of all time?
>> Well, I mean, I feel like a big thing
about him is this that I saw. I feel
it's a really big character thing, too,
is the fact that he played 10 years and
didn't miss a snap. I feel that was like
the biggest thing at first where it was
like I think that's insane because
there's you there's you know there's no
way that he got through 10 seasons
healthy and the fact that he never
missed a snap. Um I think that just as
like a when I was younger too showed me
like his character um and how well he
played those 10 seasons too or his whole
career. Um to me it's it's kind of
undeniable that he's the greatest of all
time.
reading that letter you wrote to to GM
and you called yourself you said you're
the best receiver in the draft class. I
guess what makes you say that? What
gives you that confidence to say that?
>> Um like I said before, you know, um you
know, um I'm very confident. Um I feel
like, you know, um I I feel like, you
know, I am the you know, I feel like I
am the most versatile. I feel like um I
feel like I feel like I am the I feel
like I feel like I am the best you know
playmaker you know um you know you know
um about a group but you know uh
everybody you know um is amazing you
know um everybody you know um you know
uh everybody has you know everybody has
their you know um
everybody has things you know that um
everybody has their things that let you
know that everybody does well. So,
>> just address the fact that Andrew Barry
uh when he talked to us, he told us that
after he read your letter that he
actually picked up the phone and called
you uh to tell you uh just how much that
moved him. Uh what did it mean to you to
hear from him in those words when you
weren't even sure if you were going to
be here or not? And you know, how did
you feel about that?
>> You know, uh it meant a lot. Um you you
know um just you know having him you
know um read the letter you know um you
know um you know him you know um and him
you know reaching out you know um and
showing love and support. both, you
know, uh, you know, this obviously
you're taking in the experience of being
drafted by a team. You'll do that, but
how eager are you for the next step of
getting to work on these practice fields
and taking part of rookie mini camp and
really getting to fit into this
organization?
>> Yeah, I'm just I'm excited. So, because
I know there's going to be a learning
curve. I mean, I'm going against dudes
that are bigger, faster, stronger than
guys I've ever gone against. So, I'm
excited to um to be able to take that
challenge head on and just get better.
Yeah. Um, honestly, you know, uh, I'm
just ready to work also. Um, I'm ready
to comp. Uh, I'm ready to, you know,
compete. Um, I love competing. Um, so,
you know, uh, honestly, you know, uh,
I'm just, you know, eager, you know, uh,
excited. Um, I'm ready to get to work.
>> There was a report that you had like a
node in March. Just how you feeling um,
you know, physically and you think
you'll be like ready to go for for camp?
>> Yeah. Um, I had a niece code March 12th,
I think about five weeks out. Um, I feel
great. I'm back running. I'm back
running routes. I'm back lifting. So,
you know, um, by the time, you know, the
rookie mini camp comes, like I'm ready
to go.
>> Talked a lot about, you know, football
stuff. But talk about some of the people
that you have that you brought here and
kind of the influence they played in you
getting to this point.
>> Yeah, I just brought my my fiance, my
beautiful fiance Sammy. Um, I would have
my parents here, but my brother's in the
draft as well, so they're at home with
him. Um, but just so I'll speak as if my
parents were here as well. Um, uh, they
my both my parents just sacrificed
everything all going up for me to get to
where I'm at today. Um, yeah, there was
no sacrifice too great for them. And
then, uh, her, she just been the
greatest support of my life. There was,
uh, some dog days, um, some days that I
was real sick during the season and she
was the one nursing me. So, um, yeah,
I've just had a lot of incredible
support.
>> Yeah. Uh, so above there, I I got my
dad, my mom, you know, um,
my beautiful girlfriend. Um, my dad, you
know, um, he's the one that, you know,
um, he put the football in my hand. Uh,
since, you know, four years old. um you
know uh he just he's just you know he's
just you know been you know that you
know person who you know um who
motivates me who you know uh who pushes
me you know to my limits uh my mom you
know um you know um the sacrifices you
know um she had to make uh you know uh I
got I got you know four little brothers
in the house so you know um so you know
uh it was just hers so you know so you
know just you know seeing her you know
um sacrifice That's a lot, you know. Uh
it meant a lot. And you know, uh my
girlfriend, you know, um she has she has
been nothing but, you know, um
supportive. Um yeah, uh she's
just been, you know, um the greatest
supporter. Um a shoulder to lean on, you
know, um and an outlet to, you know,
talk to.
Can you talk about the um the fact that
I mean I've been watching some of your
film and your tape and your your route
running is obviously one of your
strengths and you're joining Jerry Judy
here uh who is also a great route runner
and prides himself on that. Have you
watched some of Jerry? Have you watched
Jerry film at all to
>> Of course.
>> So can you just kind of talk about him
as a route runner and how you guys might
be together in that way?
>> Yeah. Um yeah, uh of course, you know,
um growing up, you know, uh Alabama, you
know, uh it was a powerhouse. Um just
seeing those guys, you know, uh be
there, you know, um you know, um and
dominate. So, you know, uh once I'm once
I'm finally able to get to, you know, um
meet him, um you know, um and pick his
brain, uh I feel like I feel like me and
his game are going to are going to
compliment are going to complement each
other very very well.
>> There's been a lot said with some of the
new offensive linemen that have come in
this off seasonason about George Warhop
and kind of what he brings to the table
as a coach. just how much were you able
to if at all interface with him during
the pre-draft process and how excited
are you to to work under him?
>> Um uh I was able to meet him at the at
the combine and on my 30 visit and I
I've it's been awesome. It's been really
awesome to get to know him, meet him. Um
just talking with him I already know I I
can I already tell what kind of coach he
is. He's definitely an old school an old
school type of coach. Um a very hardcore
type of coach and I that's all I've had.
Um, so I think yeah, that'll be awesome.
>> Assume this is a, you know, lifelong
dream for both of you guys. I'm just
curious. When you were a kid, what part
of it did you dream about? Was it
playing? Was it hearing your name
called? What was it?
>> I would say I would say, you know, just
playing honestly. Um, you know, you
know, uh, it really didn't matter, you
know, um,
if I got my name called or not. you
know, uh, you know, uh, you know, uh,
just being able to, you know, um, just
being able to play the game, you know,
that I've that just being able to play
the game that I have loved, you know, as
a kid, honestly.
>> Oh, sorry. I was I was just going to
say, um, I feel like every part of it
has been my dream. Um, hearing my name
called, I mean um, even being here I
feel like has been is a dream to me. Um,
and then getting out to play on Sundays.
Um, I'm really grateful because I feel
like just every day I'm out here, I'm in
this league is going to be like I'm
living my dream cuz I am.
>> And this question uh would be for both
of you as well. And that is it's it's
not every year that you have two first
round picks. So, I mean, have you guys
kind of had a chance to sort of talk to
each other a little bit about how you
can be a huge part of the evolution or
the transformation of this offense and
kind of uh Andrew Barry was saying that,
you know, your culture setters and
things like that. So, do you feel like
you can be uh part of something big here
to get this thing turned around?
>> Yeah, let's do it, man.
>> Yeah, let's do it.
>> Let's do it. and not be able to like uh
really really like you know um
we we really like you know um just met
you know um so you know um just you know
um coming in you know um together um and
just you know um and just you know and
leaning on each other um you know uh
helping each other out you know um and
just you know um and just you know and
and just you know and just establishing
you know
that brotherhood honestly.
>> When you were a kid growing up playing,
did you pretend you're some receiver
like whoever it might be?
>> No. So, uh, actually I I actually grew
up playing a quarterback, honestly. Uh,
I didn't I didn't um I didn't start
playing receiver until my ninth grade
year in uh high school. But I mean, um,
growing up, uh, I used to watch a lot of
Tayvon Austin. Yeah. He, you know, uh,
you know, uh, back then, you know, um,
his, you know, um, his, you know,
college highlights were, you know, were
legendary.
>> What do you make of the big deal that
was made about your arm length and in
the whole pre-draft process? At any time
were you worried that that was going to
move you down the board or keep you from
playing tackle at this level?
>> No, it's been confusing. We were talking
to someone before. It's like, shoot, I
don't even know what my real arm length
is. I mean, uh, we measured like 32 and
1/8. Uh, freaking proday was different.
Here when I came out with 30 visit, it
was 33. Was it the Steelers? It was 33.
I don't I don't know what it's like to
have 35 inch arms and it hasn't made too
much of a difference. So,
>> you think that's an overrated aspect of
the NFL draft combine process?
I mean, I I feel like I'm sure it has
something to do with it. I mean, I don't
I don't think people would make such a
big deal out of it if it wasn't a thing,
but I don't think anyone has the
athleticism and the feet that I have.
So, I fig in my case, I don't think it
makes a big a big difference.
>> Yesterday, Andrew mentioned to you that
they thought that you were the best punt
returner in the class. Just how have you
embraced that part of the game and and
are you looking forward to making waves
here?
>> Oh, yes, always. you know, um it's just,
you know, um it's just it's just, you
know, it is just it is just another way,
um I can, you know, impact the game. Um
you know, um you know, um you know, uh
it change the game. Um it just it it
just honestly adds on, you know, to my
value.
How about the fact that you are joining
an offensive line that's in the middle
of a complete massive overhaul and that
pretty much everybody at every single
position is going to be new and
different? How might that benefit you uh
you know to just kind of be on the
ground floor of a startup line?
>> Um I feel like I don't know. It's going
to be exciting. I mean, it's going to be
I'll have a It'll be really fun to have
all of us come in at the same time so we
can all kind of build relationships at
the same time. Um, I don't know. It's
It's cool not going into a room where
everyone's already, I don't know, set in
stone to be able to go in a room where
we can all build relationships at the
same time. And I'm excited to be
everybody's shadow um to kind of learn
uh how to be great in this league.
What about the the draft process,
talking to the Browns, meeting with the
Browns, and then being drafted by the
Browns has you excited about the city,
about the the organization? What gets
you excited to be here?
>> I mean, honestly, you know, just, you
know, um the relationships, you know, um
you know, uh everybody, you know, um
everybody, you know, inside the
building, you know, um you know, um from
what I can see is close. um if it feels
like you know um a family environment so
you know uh so you know so you know just
being able to be in that type of
environment.
>> Yeah. And then yeah my two favorite
things so far have been first definitely
the relationships. Um I mean meeting
coach Monkin was so cool. He's such an
awesome he's a great man. Um great
coach. Uh meeting with coach Hob I mean
I'm really I'm so excited to play for
him. And uh my second favorite thing has
actually just been the traffic here. Um
it's been unbelievable. I freaking we
was here at 5:00 p.m. during my freaking
uh my 30 and then there was no there was
nothing. There was nothing. There was
like just straight green lights. So I
was like yeah that was unbelievable.
>> Was there a moment for
>> Was there a moment for either one of you
guys during your visit that you thought
wow this could be my landing spot?
Um,
I would say I would say probably
um
I would say my I would say my my uh walk
through um after you know um we had you
know had you know um our walk through uh
we like you know um
like you know uh
we shot like hoops um you know uh it was
just you know um bonding and more, you
know, um
getting getting to getting getting to
know, you know, um each other more. And
and I feel like, you know, uh after
that, you know, it was, you know, I felt
like after that, it was a it was a
strong possibility that if I was there
at at uh 24, I could, you know, become a
a a a Cleveland Brown for sure.
>> Yeah. And I I drove here straight after
the like straight from the combine. and
they drove me here. I feel like that
alone I was like I thought it was pretty
cool and I could see myself being here.
>> The arm length stuff the the one nitpick
on you has been has been the drops. How
do you ease those concerns when someone
brings them up to you? I mean you know
um I just you know uh accepted you know
um you know uh I have I have you know
had you know drops but you know it's
more so you know um
it it is more so you know
concentration um you know uh just you
know focusing on the balls. So you know
um I've been I've been working you know
non-stop at it um every day. So, you
know, um it's gonna get fixed for sure.
>> What about um stepping into
a quarterback competition? So, both of
you guys are going to be, you know, part
of that. You probably haven't had a
whole lot of time to think about that
yet, but you know, what do you kind of
know so far a little bit maybe about
Deshawn Watson, Shador Sanders, and you
know, how maybe exciting is it to to see
this whole thing play out?
I mean, just as a lineman, it's um I'm
excited to play for for any for to play
in front of either of them. I mean, it's
so funny hearing Deshun Watson. It's
kind of like a celebrity name to me. Um
but and then I was able to play against
Shadur in college, too. Uh we we went
one-on-one. He beat us uh the last the
year before he left. But um to me, it
doesn't really matter to me. I'll my job
is to block for whoever's back there.
Yeah, I would say, you know, um
both of both both both both of those
guys, you know, um are legendary. Um you
know, uh honestly honestly to me, you
know, um you know, um it doesn't matter,
you know, um
you know, uh it's my job, you know, to
get open, you know, um you know, um
and catch the ball. So, you know, uh,
whoever is back there, you know, um,
I'll just you, you know, I'll just be,
you know, um, happy for those guys.
>> All right. Thanks, everybody.
Casey and Spencer, do you want to stand
up?
>> Oh, this is so tough.
>> What? This is a crazy crazy
>> bro.
>> Okay, you want to step down for a
second.